Terrifier 4 is a horror, thriller film directed by Damien Leone.
The fourth installment in the Terrifier franchise.
Plot TBA; Art the Clown's origins will be explored.
Sienna Shaw, played by Lauren LaVera.
Art the Clown, played by David Howard Thornton.
Gabbie Shaw, played by Antonella Rose.
Jonathan Shaw, played by Elliott Fullam.
Twisted is an upcoming American horror-thriller film directed by Darren Lynn
Bousman and written by Jonathan Bernstein and James Greer.
It stars Djimon Hounsou, Lauren LaVera, Mia Healey, Gina
Philips, Neal McDonough, and Alicia Witt.
The film is set to be distributed by Republic Pictures, with a
digital VOD release scheduled for February 6, 2026.
The film explores themes of monster, clown, sequel, prequel, slasher.
The tone is dark and intense.